# **Cindy Chang Front-End / UX Developer**

#### **About Me**

I am a 37-year-old Front-End / UX Developer, originally from California but now residing in the Netherlands. I love the intersection between design and development and started as a graphic designer and now work as a Front-End and UX developer. I am driven by a desire to constantly grow in my personal and professional life.

## **Experience**

#### Front-End / UX Developer (Creative Fabrica)

2019-present - Netherlands

- Front-End development for migrating existing Wordpress site to React and creating new projects in React, NextJS and Tyepscript.
- Maintaining, building and improving main corporate site's front end and building new UX elements in javascript, HTML5 and SASS.
- Worked closely with stakeholders, designers and backend developers to build and modify existing features on the site.

## Front-End Designer (Freelance)

2018-2019 - New Orleans

- Front-end design, UI/UX for various clients. Working with sites built
  with various static site generators such as Hugo and Jekyll and
  CMS platforms such as Craft and Wordpress.
- Worked directly with stakeholders: wireframing, prototyping, design, build-out, developer collaboration and troubleshooting.

### **Design & Web Development** (Domino Data Lab)

2016-2018 - New Orleans, Louisiana

- Lead Creative for the Marketing team, working closely with major stakeholders to create web and graphic solutions for a rapidly scaling startup in a constantly evolving data science landscape.
- Designed, developed and maintained main corporate website, blog and event websites run on Jekyll and Wordpress.
- Created branding for Strata Conferences and all company led events.

#### Graphic & Web Design (Industry44)

2010-2014 - Montreal, Quebec

- Lead web designer for small web studio.
- Designed all websites and worked with developers for implementation.
- In charge of all graphic design (business cards, magazine advertisements and brochures).



- **\** 31 0638091532
- cindychang.co
- cindychangy

#### Education

San Francisco State University
Marketing Communications, 2002

## Design

Sketch

Figma

Adobe Creative Suite

Invision

#### Dev

React

NextJS

JavaScript

**Typescript** 

Jest

HTML5

CSS3

SASS

PHP (Wordpress)

**NPM Scripts** 

**GIT** 

#### **Hobbies**

I love to travel, blog about true crime, bake, do crossfit and watch ice hockey (Go Red Wings).